Contact

adam@fromthemachine.org

www.linkedin.com/in/adam5 (LinkedIn) fromthemachine.org (Blog) getme.s.lamc.la (Other)

Top Skills

Outsourcing Management Programming

Languages

C++ (Full Professional)
Java (Professional Working)
Python (Professional Working)

Publications

sHeOLYit

antagonizing pain

Time and Chance, Saturn and Son... RLNY

Know me as Adam

XIV: ORVER ET AUT

Adam Marshall Dobrin

IT, SQL, Python ... "magic words" ... and "up to Earth" insight. Los Angeles, California

Summary

I have worked for over two decades in the computer industry; in development, system and database administration, and have a sincere and deep lust for science and new technologies. Recently I've begun writing about a "hidden" yet very tangible relationship between computer technology and religion, focusing on verifying proof of this connection both in ancient mythology and in the manifestation of these ideas in modern research and development in the names and works of modern companies.

I have a passion for the ethos and beneficence of open source technology; and believe that the transparent and open collaboration shining through this movement is a key component in the drive to see the light of a fusion of social processes and technology that has the ability to bring us into a new era of prosperity.

Experience

Ministry of Forbidden Knowledge It's passed ... "down to you" ... just kidding. April 2012 - Present (8 years) Coasta Mesa, CA

I write about a fusion of ancient myth and popular culture that yields the beginning of a narrative about turning Hell into Heaven. It focuses on technologies both hidden and in plain sight, and a message which describes how we can use this things to build the better world that we all deserve, and hope for.

This message comes to us from "on high" and describes in detail a number of modern social problems which are currently being adversely effected by these very same technologies. With only a bit of thought, it's clear to see that what we see around us is a sort of "primer" in just what not to do--somewhere between "conditioning" and "teaching," we are being prepared to be the

salvation of the Universe--the end of secrecy, and control--we are together the light of day.

http://climax.s.lamc.la

ERMC Global Services Senior Vice President 2010 - 2016 (6 years)

ERMC Corp provides BPO services to companies of all sizes. B2B products focus on easing the risks of employment, relieving business owners and management from otherwise mundane and complex tasks.

Viasensa Corp Partner 2009 - January 2010 (1 year)

Emplify, LLC IT Administrator January 2005 - June 2009 (4 years 6 months)

Setup IS infrastructure, from Asterisk PBX, open source CRM, Jabberd, Zimbra Email Suite.

Managed installation of F.W. Davison's HRPyramid on RHEL, created data export and reporting system for custom built data warehouse created from HRP's PICK database.

Administered several Linux servers, open source and proprietary database systems.

Assisted with management human resources and payroll operations.

EA ClamCo

Owner

July 2008 - 2009 (1 year)

We provide end to end consulting services for mid sized staffing companies and professional employer organizations throughout the United States.

We currently have over 2.5 million in net revenue, and provide services ranging from information technology outsourcing, to loss control and risk management.

At EA I am responsible for direct communication with top level management at our clients, oversight of the IS infrastructure, and have P&L responsibilities.

Oasis Outsourcing

Consultant

2005 - 2005 (less than a year)

Built custom Crystal Reports and interface modifications into a SalesLogix 2005 system. Provided guidance and testing for a large scale upgrade of SLX.

Certified HR Services

WC Manager / IS

January 2003 - December 2004 (2 years)

Responsible for data gathering and production of management and executive reports. Designed weekly revenue and cost analysis reports, sales reports, and operations management reports.

Built a data warehouse, using MS SQL Server, in order to automate the export and analysis of payroll and premium data from several payroll systems, including PayPlus and ScorPEO.

Integrated loss information from several insurance carriers and TPA's into a single unified database for analysis of loss ratio's, production of internal loss runs, and client profitability.

Managed, customized, and partially created a highly customized SalesLogix implementation.

Cura Group
Information Analyst

January 1999 - July 2004 (5 years 7 months)

Education

Florida Atlantic University

Bachelor of Applied Science (B.A.Sc.), Artificial Intelligence · (2000 - 2006)

University of Florida

PTS, TLES, ICS · (2000 - 2003)

Pine Crest

Master of Library & Information Science (M.L.I.S.), Egyptian Mythology and Torah Studies · (1994 - 1999)

Nova Southeastern University

Messianic Spectacle, Ancient Sumerian Mythology · (1984 - 1986)

Florida Gulf Coast University

Juris Doctor (J.D.), Early Christianity · (2011 - 2012)